Based on a true story, ‘Rise’ sees Will wrongly accused then stripped of his career and freedom, he must
survive maximum security prison and the infamous Jimmy Cove to prove his innocence...
Rise is a crime, thriller, drama film directed by Mack Lindon.
The true story of a young man falsely accused of rape and
sentenced to six years in a maximum security prison.
He must rely on survival skills and an unlikely bond with an infamous
inmate to prove his innocence and regain his freedom.
Jimmy, played by Martin Sacks.
Amber, played by Jessica Green.
Will McIntyre, played by Nathan Wilson.
Julie Nile, played by Erin Connor.
Fung Poi, played by Marty Rhone.
Butch, played by Jamie Josephs.
Rise is a 2014 Australian crime drama film.
It was written and directed by Mack Lindon and stars Nathan
Wilson as a man falsely accused of rape.
The film is based on Lindon's own experiences.
The film explores themes of underdog, rise and fall, wrongful imprisonment.
The tone is emotional and intense.